export default [
    {
        question: 'Which data type is a sequence of characters?',
        options: ['String', 'Integer', 'Float', 'Boolean', 'Array'],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'Which data type is a non-decimal number between -2,147,483,648 and 2,147,483,647?',
        options: ['Float', 'Object', 'NULL', 'Resource', 'Integer'],
        correct: 4
    },    
    {
        question: 'Which data type is a number with a decimal point or a number in exponential form?',
        options: ['NULL', 'Float', 'Resource', 'String', 'Object'],
        correct: 1
    },    
    {
        question: 'Which data type represents two possible states: TRUE or FALSE?',
        options: ['Resource', 'Array', 'Boolean', 'Object', 'NULL'],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which data type stores multiple values in one single variable?',
        options: ['Object', 'NULL', 'String', 'Resource', 'Array'],
        correct: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'Which data type stores data and information on how to process that data?',
        options: ['Resource', 'Integer', 'Object', 'Float', 'NULL'],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which data type can have only one value?',
        options: ['Boolean', 'String', 'Resource', 'NULL', 'Array'],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Which data type is not an actual data type?',
        options: ['NULL', 'Array', 'Boolean', 'Object', 'Resource'],
        correct: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'Which operator is a modulus operator?',
        options: ['**', '*', '%', '+', '/'],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which operator is a exponentiation operator?',
        options: ['/', '+', '-', '*', '**'],
        correct: 4
    }
]